<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>PinGodGame (AutoLoaded) on PinGod.VP Examples</title><link>https://horseyhorsey.github.io/PinGod.VP.Examples/pingodgame/</link><description>Recent content in PinGodGame (AutoLoaded) on PinGod.VP Examples</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 15:26:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://horseyhorsey.github.io/PinGod.VP.Examples/pingodgame/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>MachineConfig (Items)</title><link>https://horseyhorsey.github.io/PinGod.VP.Examples/pingodgame/items/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 15:26:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://horseyhorsey.github.io/PinGod.VP.Examples/pingodgame/items/</guid><description>In the game/PinGodGame.tscn scenes inspector in Godot editor you can edit the machines Coils, Switches, Lamps, Leds.
This can be accessed from the MachineConfig scene by selecting it.
When the game is loaded these items will be added to the machine.
They can be accessed inside the Machine.cs or use the PinGodGame helper methods with the item name.
When adding from the UI (green box) select String and Int for the value but it&amp;rsquo;s probably quicker to edit this file in text and add your items there with name and number.</description></item><item><title>Ball Trough (Scene)</title><link>https://horseyhorsey.github.io/PinGod.VP.Examples/pingodgame/trough/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 15:26:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://horseyhorsey.github.io/PinGod.VP.Examples/pingodgame/trough/</guid><description>Included in the examples PinGodGame.tscn tree.
Most cases you will leave the default settings here, but you can add more switches from this.
Ball search options Enabled Ball Search coils to pulse (usually saucers, scoops not the trough) Search stop switches = Switches that stop the search Search wait time = Time to wait before pulsing coils Trough / Ball Save Options Ball save seconds Ball save lamp name Ball save multiball seconds Early Ball Save switches Number of Balls to Save Trough Solenoid(coil) Trough switches Plunger lane switch Set what to do on ball started</description></item><item><title>AudioManager</title><link>https://horseyhorsey.github.io/PinGod.VP.Examples/pingodgame/audiomanager/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 15:26:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://horseyhorsey.github.io/PinGod.VP.Examples/pingodgame/audiomanager/</guid><description>AudioManager Add global music, sfx, voice sounds.
See AudioManager</description></item><item><title>Overlays (Developing)</title><link>https://horseyhorsey.github.io/PinGod.VP.Examples/pingodgame/devoverlays/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 15:26:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://horseyhorsey.github.io/PinGod.VP.Examples/pingodgame/devoverlays/</guid><description>Scenes to overlay on screen like switches and light states
Lamp Overlay Enabled This enables the LampMatrix in the DevOverlays. Options are available on the LampMatrix to change coloumns and count. Customize in your own game if need more advanced.
Switch Overlay Enabled This enables the SwitchOverlay in the DevOverlays. Options are available on the SwitchOverlay to change coloumns.
Switches can be clicked on screen.</description></item><item><title>PinGodGame.tscn - Scene</title><link>https://horseyhorsey.github.io/PinGod.VP.Examples/pingodgame/pingodgame.tscn/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 15:26:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://horseyhorsey.github.io/PinGod.VP.Examples/pingodgame/pingodgame.tscn/</guid><description>res:// paths for assets Quicker to add asset paths here</description></item><item><title>PinGodGame.cs - Script</title><link>https://horseyhorsey.github.io/PinGod.VP.Examples/pingodgame/pingodgame.cs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 15:26:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://horseyhorsey.github.io/PinGod.VP.Examples/pingodgame/pingodgame.cs/</guid><description>This script is autoloaded from the scene when the display window is launched and has many methods.
Modes and other scenes can get access to this from the root tree. GetNode&amp;lt;PinGodGame&amp;gt;(&amp;quot;/root/PinGodGame&amp;quot;).
Godot - Overrides _EnterTree = Gets user cmd line args, loads data and settings, creates trough, sets up ball search and audio manager
_Ready = Game initialized. Memory map is created here if read and write is enabled. Gets BallSearchOptions, sets up a _lampMatrixOverlay Gets hold of the MainScene to control window size, stretch</description></item><item><title>Logging Games</title><link>https://horseyhorsey.github.io/PinGod.VP.Examples/pingodgame/logging/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 15:26:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://horseyhorsey.github.io/PinGod.VP.Examples/pingodgame/logging/</guid><description>Game logging
void LogDebug(params object[] what); void LogInfo(params object[] what); void LogWarning(string message = null, params object[] what); void LogError(string message = null, params object[] what); PinGodLogLevel LogLevel { get; } For example:
pinGod.LogInfo(&amp;quot;my message&amp;quot;);
Log location In the game name appdata directory. Use the open_app_data.bat to open directory instead of looking for it.</description></item><item><title>Recording / Playback</title><link>https://horseyhorsey.github.io/PinGod.VP.Examples/pingodgame/recordings-playback/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 15:26:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://horseyhorsey.github.io/PinGod.VP.Examples/pingodgame/recordings-playback/</guid><description>Quick guide on how to record and playback a game. Recording a game can speed up your game development for game logic.
They would usually start off by using trough switches adding credits and starting a game, then any events after this to test any recorded sequence.
Recording Recording files are saved in the user://recordings/recordname.record
Example game dir: C:\Users\UserName\AppData\Roaming\Godot\app_userdata\BasicGameGodot\recordings
&amp;nbsp;Note You can get to the app_data directory for the game using app_data bat file</description></item></channel></rss>